Using only song names from ONE ARTIST, cleverly answer these questions. Pass it on to at least 15 people and include me. You can't use the band I used. Try not to repeat a song title. It's a lot harder than you think! Repost as "my life according to (band name)"
 
ARTIST: GONG 
￼ 

Are you a male or female?
Digital Man
 
Describe yourself:
Working Man
 
How do you feel:
In the Mood
 
Describe where you currently live:
La Villa Strangiato
 
If you could go anywhere, where would you go:
The Twilight Zone
 
Your favorite form of transportation:
Red Barchetta
 
Your best friend is:
Tom Sawyer
 
What's the weather like:
Tears
 
Favorite time of day:
2112
 
If your life was a TV show, what would it be called:
The Spirit of the Radio
 
What is life to you:
Lessons
 
Your fear:
Cygnus X-1
 
What is the best advice you have to give:
Take A Friend
 
Thought for the Day:
Time Stand Still
 
How I would like to die:
Cold Fire
 
My soul's present condition:
YYZ
 
My motto:
Something for Nothing